hostcob.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy

**Last updated 8 January 2013**

This privacy policy describes how hostcob.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website. At hostcob.com, we aim to provide you strongest security and privacy. By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collection

We may collect various details when you sign-up with hostcob.com & you use our services. The personal Information you give us, is collected through both automated means such as communications profiles and cookies, which may differ according to the type of service, sale, support and other inquiries. The information taken by you at the time of sign-up may include your your name, company name, email address, residential address, company address, phone number, fax number, dates of service provided, types of service provided, domain name, amount of payments, date of payments, manner of payment, payment history, credit card or other payment information. We may combine or reuse the information provided by you in order to provide you a better user experience. Any billing details collected by us, only be used to bill you for the domains, products and services you purchased. If you purchase domain, product or any other service by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider by our secure payment gateway. All sensitive information like payment or billing details are collected by a secure server. All the payment or billing information are transferred through a secure sockets layer certified interface. 

## Information Use

The information collected by us, is used to provide you services, billing interface and support as a HostCob customer. When needed we may also use the information for such purposes like introducing you with our new services, maintaining/improving our services, communicating with customers and ensuring up-time and reliability. We may also study and analyse the information any time to determine our customers needs and provide best customer satisfaction. You may get the HostCob monthly newsletter to your primary contact e-mail, which will be having the notification of services or billing. HostCob customers have the right to opt out of these newsletters at any time. 

## No-Spam Policy

We use a strict No-Spam Policy to prohibit the use of any data collected to send spam. We will not sell any contact information to third parties. 

## Cookies

Cookies are small text files that store information which allows a website to manage session and recognize your account. Our website hostcob.com also uses cookies to determine/manage session, temporarily hold your log-in details, and provide personalized functionality. Most browsers like Internet Explorer, Mozilla and Chrome are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser any time to refuse all cookies. If hostcob.com sign-up and payment modules get your browser in cookies-off mode, it will use "url rewritting" to determine your session. 

## Log Files

When you log on to hostcob.com, we use IP addresses to analyze client-server experience, track access, and gather visitor demographic information for providing better user experience. IP addresses are not linked to your personally identifiable information. We provide all the services in secure environment and check every order with our security tools to protect against fraud. May may store your IP address at the time of placing any order to maintain the secure environment. 

## Information Sharing

We may share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are mentioned in this statement. We do not sell our client's personal information to third parties. We may provide some of your personal information to companies that provide us services to serve you better such as customer service (live chat) or payment gateways. We ensure you, these companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also disclose your personal information as required by cyber law or any similar legal process. 

## Updating Personal & Contact Information

At hostcob.com, we provide you full access to your personal and contact information. You can complete, correct or update your personal and contact information at any time. 

## Links to Other Web Sites

Our website hostcob.com may include external links to other websites whose privacy policies may differ from HOSTCOB SOLUTIONS. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is handled according to their own privacy policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We regularly try to improve our services and support. In order to provide your better experience, we can improve this privacy policy time to time. (Last updated 8 January 2013) 

## Contact Information

If you get any query in mind about this privacy policy, you can contact us about this privacy policy by writing or email us at the address below:  
**HOSTCOB SOLUTIONS**  
2nd Floor, JN Plaza,  
Haridwar Road  
Dehradun - 248001  
Uttarakhand  
India  
+91 97 6050 6090  
Email: _info@hostcob.com_
